Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
- Yoko.
- What is wrong?
I'm just leaving
the Williams' house now.
Jennifer's out
and Emma's asleep.
I'll leave the keys with Alex
at the care center
before I head to the airport.
- Did something happen?
- No. I...
- What is wrong?
- I need to go home.
I know I made
a longer commitment.
but I need to get back
to my family.
I can't explain it.
It's like something...
I just need to get back
to the States.
You were
supposed to stay for a few...
Yoko? Yoko?
Yoko.
Where...?
- Oh. hey.
- Mommy!
- You guys. I'm home.
- Welcome back.
- You made it. Heh. heh.
- Oh. my love.
Welcome home.
Oh. it's so good to be home.
- I missed you.
Burke? Time to go!
Burke.
Burke?
Hey. what you doing. bud?
What's going on?
Come on. we gotta go now.
Stop playing with that.
Me and Daddy never finished it.
Come here.
I miss Daddy.
I miss him too.
So much.
And that's okay
because we're supposed to.
I think this move's gonna be
really good for us.
It's gonna be a new place.
And a new start.
Nothing bad's gonna
happen to me. okay?
Nothing bad's gonna happen
to you either.
I promise.
And it means more
because I'm a police officer.
Come on. I know
first days are hard.
but you gotta do it.
like ripping off a Band-Aid.
I'm scared.
I'm scared too.
What do we do
when we're scared?
Close your eyes
and count to five.
Right.
One. two. three...
four...
five.
Everything's okay.
Let's go to school.
Ready?
"The lights are on.
but nobody's home."
I hear they stuck
you with the new chick.
Don't call them
"chicks."
Buddy of mine in Vice said
her old man died of cancer.
Real brutal. Kid was
alone with him when he died.
It's only been three months.
Muldoon?
Yeah.
Smoke?
Nah. I quit.
Mind if I do?
Go ahead.
How are you
liking it around here?
Uh. we're still
getting settled in.
It's definitely different.
How does something
like this even happen?
Car's been here for months.
Doors were locked
when we found it.
Gruesome. huh?
I'll say.
Got an ID yet?
Sure do.
Got Lorna Moody. 65.
Why did it take so long
to find her?
Well. this here's
a service road.
They only just started
using it for the season.
Anyone come looking for her?
That's just it. The feds.
they're already looking for her.
Turns out she's one of those
assisted-suicide broads.
Find anything on her?
Usual stuff.
I got an address though.
Directions
in the glove box.
44 Reyburn Drive.
Same place
as the Landers case.
Looks like
we got another one.
Another what?
What was
the Landers case?
Anything else?
Forensics will be here soon.
The FBI is on its way too.
Sure looks like something
was in there with her.
You ever seen anything
like this one before?
Detective...
What's up with
the Landers house?
Worked a case there.
two years ago.
- Sort of stuck with me.
- Mm.
And it's...
just strange to see it
pop up again.
Maybe they're connected.
It's just a weird coincidence.
"Entire family murdered."
Hey! Put that shit away
before Goodman sees you.
- Why?
- He worked that case there.
He never set foot inside.
Never seen a cop do that before.
Hello?
Police department.
I just want to go.
Hello?
Police department.
I just want to go.
Will you take me?
- Hello?
- Take me home.
I don't want to be here.
Chicken for dinner.
We're gonna have...
Are you Mrs. Matheson?
I'm Detective Muldoon.
Gonna talk to you
about a woman we found.
Will you feed me?
Excuse me?
William. my...
He always used to
feed me.
William was your husband?
Ma'am. are you alone
in the house right now?
Will you help me. please?
Help me.
Help me. help me.
Please! No. please!
Don't leave!
- Stay there. I'm gonna get help.
- No. no. no! No!
Help me!
No!
Don't leave me!
Don't leave me.
Do not leave me!
Please don't leave me.
Don't leave...
Car 646. we need an ambulance
to 44 Reyburn Drive.
What the fuck was that?
I heard you the first time!
What are you doing here?
I went to the house.
There's another body.
Come in.
This is my body.
which is given...
The Landers was just...
one of those cases.
Total mess.
Whole family murdered
at the house on Reyburn.
The neighbors too.
Fiona Landers...
She murdered
her 6-year-old daughter.
And then she killed
her husband.
And then herself.
You think the body
that we found was related?
I can't go down
the same road again.
Why did you never
go into the house?
Something never
felt right about it.
Just...
didn't feel right.
What do you mean?
My old partner. he was obsessed.
He said there was...
energy.
Mm. spirits.
Something like that.
You saying
the house is haunted?
People will think you're crazy
if you start
saying shit like that.
Yeah. well. I don't buy that.
I'm sorry. can I
get you anything?
No. I'm good.
Pie?
- Not that pie.
- Oh. fuck.
Heh. I'm good.
My mother...
she was into
all that ghostly shit.
The older I get.
the more I wanna believe it.
Mm-hm.
- She passed away. huh?
- Yeah.
I just don't have the heart
to get rid of all this.
I still think of this as...
her house.
Yeah. I understand
how that goes.
- How long for you?
- Three months.
It was cancer.
I've seen
how that plays out.
I don't wish that on anyone.
I get you're looking
for distractions right now.
Don't get lost
in this shit.
The case. the house...
I know what that looks like.
Neonatal oncologist to OR 3.
Don't worry. Amnios are
pretty routine for women your age.
Mm-hm. I'm... I'm ready. thanks.
Okay.
This is the poke.
Mm-hm.
That's the needle.
Does it hurt?
No. It's okay.
This is where
you're gonna feel a cramp.
I have the results.
The amnio confirmed
what we suspected
from the blood work.
The likelihood that your child
will be born with ALD is high.
I know that we've. uh.
previously discussed
various possibilities...
but if you have
any questions now.
I can put you in touch
with some other families.
Helps to hear from other parents
about the realities of this.
But. uh...
there's still a chance. right?
That our baby
will be born healthy?
Reyburn's coming up.
I wanna stop by
and get
the Landers' signature.
Wait. uh...? We have
to do that right now?
- I wanna get it done today.
- Okay.
Be right back.
Hello?
Peter Spencer.
Anybody home?
Peter Spencer here.
Hello?
Peter Spencer.
Oh. my God.
Okay.
Unbelievable.
The car's still here.
But nobody's home.
I might have to come back again
tomorrow morning.
So we're not gonna
talk about it?
I don't know
what you want me to say.
I just want you to...
I want us to talk so we can
make this decision together.
Are you mad at me?
No. No.
I'm not mad at you.
I love you.
I love you. so I wanted
to have a family with you.
- I'm not mad at you.
- I know. I love you too.
- I'm sorry.
- No.
I just don't know
what to do.
We'll figure it out.
Will you turn off
the light?
That light's so bright.
Hi.
- How you feeling?
- I don't know.
- We'll figure it out.
- Mm-hm.
Breakfast. I'm gonna
make you some breakfast.
You?
What was that?
You're gonna cook?
Yeah. I'm gonna cook.
I'm a good cook.
Wait. you're gonna
burn the place down?
I mean. that's how
we're gonna deal with this?
Yes. I'm gonna murder us
with deliciousness.
Okay.
Windy today with
gusts up to 40 miles per hour.
The temperature dropping
from 59 to...
Hello.
I'm actually
the real estate agent.
Oh. God.
You scared me.
You are...
Melinda. right?
You remember me?
I'm the guy on the sign.
Melinda. sweetheart.
are your parents home?
Oh. God.
Your nose is bleeding...
Sweetheart. let's get you
inside. Come on.
You doing okay?
I think
it's all stopped.
Yeah.
Where are your parents?
Do you know?
Let's try your dad again. huh?
Let's see
if he picks up this time.
Sam Landers. Leave a message.
Hi. Mr. Landers.
this is. uh...
This is Peter Spencer...
um. again.
I'm actually at your house
right now.
I just came by to get
those closing signatures.
Um. I will try you again later.
Um...
Your daughter is here.
Uh. she had a little bit
of a bloody nose.
but she's doing okay now.
Please give me a call
when you get this.
Mommy's friend. Yoko.
taught me how to say. "Moshi moshi."
I miss you so much.
I can't wait to come home
and squeeze you.
I... Whoop. ha!
I already have so many things
to give you.
And you're going to love them.
Bye. angel.
Mama loves you.
My name is Lorna Moody.
I'm known as an exit guide.
I sit with people
who've made the decision
to end their lives
on their own terms.
I want to start
by answering
any questions
you might have for me.
How long will
it take her to die?
Our preferred method is a gas
that requires
the use of a hood.
Once she pulls the hood
down over her head.
she'll be unconscious
in five to 10 seconds.
That's all she'll know.
How many times
have you done this?
I've been
a compassionate presence
at the bedside of 44 people.
Tell me about your wife.
We found out
she was sick last year.
She was pretty far gone...
by the time we realized.
So we moved here...
so she could be closer
to her doctors.
But after the move.
she started getting worse.
I'm so sorry.
I'm glad you called.
Hopefully. I can help.
I hope so.
Mr. Matheson.
I need to warn you.
For anyone to do this.
they must be mentally competent
and physically able to
carry it through themselves.
Is that clear?
Do you understand?
Yeah. Mm-hm.
Shall we go see your wife? Hm?
Mrs. Matheson.
my name is Lorna Moody.
Do you know why I'm here?
Your husband told me
about your condition.
and I'm here to see
if I can help.
Mrs. Matheson.
are you all right?
Peekaboo!
Who are you playing with?
My friend.
And what's your friend's name?
Melinda.
Melinda?
Is she here with us now?
- Please. I haven't said...
- Mr. Matheson.
I was quite clear
on the requirements.
and I'm truly. deeply sorry.
but your wife is no longer
mentally competent.
Please.
You can't just leave.
I am deeply sorry
for everything you and
your wife have been through...
but you misrepresented
her condition.
What am I supposed to do?
I would still like
to stay a few days.
if that's all right with you.
I may not be able to help
in the way that you wanted.
but at least I could provide
some support. no matter what.
Is that okay with you?
So. what do you like to do
at the playground?
Because I like the swings.
We can swing. swing.
Thank you.
I made up
the guest room for you.
We don't get much company.
Oh. it's lovely.
All right. well. I have to run
to the store for some dinner.
Oh. no. you don't
have to do that.
Not much in the kitchen either.
Well. let me go.
It's the least I can do.
Oh!
Hello.
Excuse me.
Excuse me. sir.
Mr. Matheson.
There's a strange man
standing on your front lawn.
I think there's
something wrong with him.
Hello?
He's here again.
- My partner?
- Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I'll be right there.
Yeah. Okay.
See you soon.
Who is he?
He's a cop.
What's he doing?
Who knows?
He worked a case here before we moved in.
Now he won't leave us alone.
A case?
I hope it wasn't a murder.
Oh. God. It was. wasn't it?
You gotta stop it
with this shit.
What's the matter with you?
Does your wife know
what's going on?
You're driving yourself crazy.
You need to leave
that family alone.
I'm sorry I've ever
said anything. man.
Just...
think about your family.
No! No. no. no! Why?
Frank.
Frank. stop.
Hi. This is
Detective Muldoon. 45632.
I'm just trying to get a 20
on a Detective Wilson.
who also used to work
at the 51.
Yeah. Just one second.
All right. ahem.
Saint Gideon's.
Isn't that
the psychiatric hospital?
All right. Thank you.
Frank.
Hi. I'm here to see
Detective Wilson.
Down the hall. to the right.
Already restrained.
Detective Wilson?
I'm Detective Muldoon.
The doctor said that she told
you I was gonna come see you.
Did you find my tapes?
Uh. your tapes. sir?
Mm.
I came to ask you
some questions
about a case that you worked
two years ago.
What can you tell me
about the Landers family?
It's happening again.
isn't it?
Once you step into the place
where they died.
it never lets you go.
This is never gonna end.
What will never end?
That house's grudge.
There she is.
You went into the Landers'
house. didn't you?
If you haven't started seeing
them yet. don't worry.
You will.
Maybe we should
tear our eyes out
so that we can't
see them anymore.
No!
It's the house!
You gotta burn it down!
Ahh! Burn it to the ground!
Wait. Kill me.
Kill me! Kill me!
Guys. he's losing blood fast!
I can still feel them
watching me!
I can still
feel them watching me!
I can't stop
thinking about the Landers' murder.
What the hell happened
in that house?
Who does that
to a 6-year-old girl?
Nobody does that to
a 6-year-old girl. A monster.
Now. ever since I went
to that house.
I've been seeing shit.
I can't get it out of my head.
There's a case I found
in Japan.
At least a dozen
unrelated people
killed in the same house
in Tokyo.
And I spoke to the detective
over there. this Nakagawa.
He thinks a murder
in that house
caused something
called a Ju-On.
Something like a curse.
Fiona Landers worked
at that same house in Tokyo.
and I know this sounds crazy.
I think Fiona Landers
brought this curse
back with her from Japan.
And it made her
kill her family.
- Where is he?
- Where do you think?
All right. all right. Focus.
Just focus. Just focus.
That's what she said
when we started.
- Hey.
- When we first started.
it was at the beginning.
I know it was.
The Landers. the real
estate agents. that thing in Japan.
they're connected.
I'm telling you.
You gotta trust me.
When was the last time
you ate?
- You look like shit.
- It's the case.
The case is cold.
Don't give me that shit.
You know something
awful's going on.
I get it.
I do.
And I wish I knew
how to help you.
Just. you know.
take some time off.
Spend some time with
the girls.
And then maybe it'll stop.
They're never gonna stop.
Never.
It's Fiona Landers.
She's the one
who's been doing this.
Let's get out of here.
Come on.
You good?
Yeah. Yeah.
- Ahh!
- What? Stop it.
- Oh. God! Ahh!
- What? Stop it!
- No! Stop it! Wilson! Wilson!
- Fucker! No! Stop her!
Fuck.
- Oh. Jesus.
- The fuck are you doing?
Sam Landers is here.
- What are you talking about?
- He's in the building.
- Sam Landers is dead.
- Come on. He's on the tape.
Don't you have a kid?
Go home.
And get some sleep.
You're losing it.
Hi. The sitter
canceled on me. so. uh...
I couldn't find anybody
at short notice.
Sit down.
Relax. You can read this.
It's kind of...
Oh. no. no. no. Right there.
Hey. It's okay. Relax.
The kid and I will find
something to do. okay?
- Come on. buddy. Come with me.
- Yeah? Yeah. you can go.
Okay.
What do we have here?
I think you can watch this.
Hello?
Hi.
Hi. Where are you?
I'm still at the house.
What time do you think
you'll be home?
Uh. I don't know.
I can't leave her by herself.
Do you think
you should call the police?
- What's the matter?
- Nothing.
The. uh...
The baby just moved.
How are you feeling
about everything?
I'm sorry.
It's not a good time. I know.
No. no. no. it's okay. Um...
I... I wanna talk about it.
Peter. I never wanted
to be a mother.
But I love this baby.
like. so much more
than I thought I did. and...
I don't know. I...
I'm gonna love this baby.
no matter what.
Peter. are you there?
Yeah. I'm still here.
I'm just really. really happy.
Was that the doorbell?
Uh. let me see who it is.
I'll call you right back. okay?
Okay. I love you.
Yeah. I love you too.
Melinda?
Melinda. sweetheart.
is that you?
Melinda?
You okay?
Hi.
Hello?
Peter.
Peter?
Oh. Jesus Christ.
You scared me.
The parents finally came home?
Hey. what's wrong?
What are you doing?
What is wrong with you?
Here. You look beautiful.
How about some pear?
Hm?
Pear?
Oh. yeah. we like pear.
don't we?
Mm.
Oh. yeah. This.
How long have you been married?
Fifty years. next month.
Oh.
Mm.
Fifty beautiful years.
You're such a good girl.
You're gonna be so happy.
Mrs. Matheson.
Mrs. Matheson?
Mrs. Math...
Hey. hey. What's wrong?
What happened?
What's the matter?
I don't want you to take this
the wrong way. but I believe...
your house...
is haunted.
I thought someone like you...
might understand our unique...
situation.
Wh...? You mean.
you've seen her too?
Mm-hm.
Seeing them...
it gives me hope that maybe
she might be around too.
After it's over.
You see. I think.
with places like this.
it feels like the walls
between this world
and the next
have been torn down.
Time acts differently here.
Anyone who has entered here
and anyone who will enter here.
we're all bound together.
When Faith goes.
this place
will let us stay together.
It's the only hope
that we have.
Mr. Matheson?
Mrs. Matheson?
I'm so happy to see you
on your feet.
Mrs. Matheson.
What have you done?
What did you do?
He wanted to kill me.
How does something
like this even happen?
Hey.
Did you get any word
on that body we found?
- The feds took over last night.
- Wait.
What about interviewing
Mrs. Matheson?
There's nothing I could do.
What about the house.
did they follow up on that?
It doesn't seem like it.
Shit like this always happens
when we turn it over
to the feds.
Don't worry about it.
I'm sure they'll send someone
by the next few days.
- Next few days?
- Yeah.
We found a fucking body
and another one in the house.
How many more
do we have to find?
Ah! Jesus. just drop it.
It's not our case anymore.
Seriously.
- Good morning. Mrs. Matheson.
- Morning.
How you doing.
Mrs. Matheson?
Thank you.
Oh. my God.
Someone get help!
Go. Go!
Hi.
you've reached the Muldoons.
We can't come
to the phone right now.
but you can leave us
a message after the beep.
Hey. It's me.
I thought you should know
that the hospital called.
Faith Matheson's dead.
Okay. Um. call me
when you get this.
It's the house!
You gotta burn it down!
This is never gonna end.
What will never end?
That house's grudge.
Burn it to the ground!
Burke?
Why did he kill them?
Did he say?
There's
someone not at rest here.
A little girl. I think.
I've spent my life
trying to communicate
with people on the other side.
And I feel this spirit
so powerfully.
He claims it was
for the insurance money.
You will not.
The dead only want
one thing. Bobby.
I know.
To go into the light.
Mom?
Burke?
What's going on?
Baby. come here.
Mom?
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
What do we do
when we're scared?
We close our eyes.
and we count to five.
- One...
two...
three...
four...
five.
See? Everything's fine.
- Goodman.
- It's Muldoon.
Can you come over?
I need to talk.
I didn't know
anyone else to call.
This is not
your case.
You have no business
going into this.
But I did.
Was this happening
at all...
before
you went to the house?
I don't know.
And. uh...
now. when I'm closing my eyes.
I can see them.
Whatever happened to Wilson
is happening to me.
And I'm scared.
I can't end up like him.
I'm afraid it's gonna
make me hurt my son.
Where are we going?
I have to try to stop this.
I need to keep you safe.
Whatever happens. do not
get out of this car. okay?
Do not open this door.
Do you understand?
Promise me?
I promise.
I love you so much.
I wanna show you something.
How could you do that?
Melinda?
I wanna show you something.
Mom?
What are you doing?
Burke.
I told you to stay in the car.
Mommy. please don't do this.
Get back in the car now.
I don't
understand.
Why are you doing this?
I'm scared.
What do we do
when we're scared?
when we're scared. Burke?
What do we do
when we're scared?
Close our eyes...
...and count to five.
One...
two...
What have you done?
- ...three...
I can still feel them
watching me!
- ...four...
five.
I love you so much.
Burke. bus is here!
Have a good day at school. bud.
Come here.
Mommy's gonna be okay.
We're both gonna be okay.
And I love you so much.
So much.
I'm going to school. Mom!
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm